this is mark thanks for watching hi this
is Mark
this is English conversation practice at
a hotel booking a room or making a
reservation hi this is Joe Smith I'm
calling because I would like to book a
room hello mr. Smith
when will you be staying with us
August 21st great is that for one night
yes it is what size room will you need
it's just me so a single bed is fine I
understand
I'll send the confirmation by email
thank you for calling you're welcome by
checking in
hi I'd like to check in my name is Joe
Smith hello mr. Smith just a moment
can you fill in this form please hotel
reservation form name date phone number
home work fax number email address date
of arrival airline and flight time of
arrival date of departure airline and
flight time of departure would you
prefer a smoking or non-smoking room
non-smoking please do you have laundry
service yes we do
just put your dirty clothes in this box
and leave it by the door
is there a gym in this hotel yes there
is it's on the second floor
your room key will open the door to the
gym
breakfast will be served from 6:00 a.m.
to 10:00 a.m. it's buffet style sounds
good
please enjoy your stay with us
I will thanks okay great job take it
easy
we'll see you next time bye